<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Responsi 1 Mobile (H1D023015)</string>
    <string name="club_name">79. CA Osasuna</string>
    <string name="club_description">Club Atlético Osasuna adalah klub sepak bola profesional yang berbasis di Pamplona, Navarre, Spanyol. Klub ini didirikan pada tahun 1920 dan berkompetisi di La Liga, divisi teratas sepak bola Spanyol. Osasuna dikenal dengan julukan "Los Rojillos" dan memiliki stadion kandang El Sadar.</string>
    <string name="club_history">Club History</string>
    <string name="head_coach">Head Coach</string>
    <string name="team_squad">Team Squad</string>
    <string name="club_history_detail">Club Atlético Osasuna, commonly known as Osasuna, is a Spanish football club based in Pamplona, Navarre. Founded on 17 October 1920, the club has a rich history spanning over a century.\n\nThe name "Osasuna" means "health" in Basque, reflecting the club\'s deep connection to the Basque culture and traditions of the region. The team plays their home matches at El Sadar stadium, which has a capacity of 23,576 spectators.\n\nThroughout their history, Osasuna has experienced both triumphs and challenges. The club has spent most of their existence alternating between the first and second divisions of Spanish football. Their most successful period came in the 1980s and early 1990s, when they established themselves as a consistent La Liga side.\n\nOne of Osasuna\'s most memorable achievements was reaching the Copa del Rey final in 2005, where they faced Real Betis. Although they lost the final, this achievement remains one of the highlights in the club\'s history.\n\nThe club is known for their passionate fanbase, known as "Los Rojillos" (The Little Reds), who create an incredible atmosphere at El Sadar. The supporters are famous for their loyalty and have stuck with the club through both good times and difficult periods.\n\nOsasuna\'s playing style has traditionally been characterized by hard work, determination, and a strong team spirit. They have produced several notable players over the years who have gone on to represent Spain at the international level.\n\nIn recent years, the club has focused on developing young talent through their academy system while maintaining their identity as a family-oriented club deeply rooted in Navarrese culture. The club continues to be an important institution in Pamplona and serves as a source of pride for the local community.\n\nDespite facing financial difficulties at various points in their history, Osasuna has always managed to overcome adversity through the support of their dedicated fans and the commitment of everyone involved with the club.</string>
</resources>